Wassim Khemici

Email: wkhemici@berkeley.edu | Mobile: 650.245.0171

Portfolio: https://wkhemici.github.io/portfolio/ | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/wkhemici/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Digital content specialist with extensive writing, editing, content management, graphic design, and marketing experience. Over 7 years of writing experience and 3 years of experience writing public-facing marketing content to audiences in the Silicon Valley and San Francisco. Specialize in writing web content. Experienced executive-level/C-Suite and PR writer. Creative with a strong technical background. Adept at quickly learning new tech/software and distilling complex technical concepts into legible language.

EDUCATION

University of California, Berkeley **Bachelor of Arts**, English (August 2016)

University of California, Berkeley Extension **Web Development Full-Stack Certificate** (May 2019)

Google Analytics Academy Certificate of Completion, Google Analytics for Beginners (September 2019)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web: HTML5, CSS, SEO (Search Engine Optimization), WordPress, Bootstrap, Github, JavaScript, Materialize Additional Software & Design: Adobe InDesign, Adobe Lightroom, Adobe Acrobat, Microsoft Suite, MailChimp, Slack, Google Typography, Google Drive, Social Media Marketing, Google Analytics

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content & Marketing Coordinator

JODI Group, Inc. | San Francisco, CA

March 2017-February 2019

- Effectively wrote, edited, and managed all of the company's written copy
- Drafted internal and public-facing communications for executives, PR, and customers
- Crafted email marketing campaigns with MailChimp & direct mail campaigns to field groups
- Significantly increased views-per-article and SEO for company blog www.49miles.com
- Conceptualized and managed content calendar for blog, social media accounts, and print
- Tastefully designed layouts with Adobe InDesign, Acrobat, & Lightroom
- Played an integral role in the development of the new company websites and blog

Freelance Writer, Tutor, and Editor

Freelance | Bay Area, CA

August 2014-Present

- Write content for Facebook Community Events to advertise to the Silicon Valley audience
- Authored advertising content for the San Mateo Daily Journal to market the County Pride Center
- Edit case studies, user-experience guides, and technical documentation for programmers
- Coach students to refine their academic writing, editing, analytic skills, and applications

Student Intern

Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching | Stanford, CA

June 2013-August 2014

- Managed the company's organizational and administrative duties
- Coordinated educational seminars and research programs
- Gathered research data and created analytical reports